Some people just want more.
Materialists is a romance, drama film directed by Celine Song.
A young, ambitious New York City matchmaker finds herself torn
between the perfect match and her imperfect ex.
Lucy, played by Dakota Johnson.
John, played by Chris Evans.
Harry, played by Pedro Pascal.
Sophie, played by Zoë Winters.
Violet, played by Marin Ireland.
Daisy, played by Dasha Nekrasova.
Materialists is a 2025 American romantic drama film
written and directed by Celine Song.
The film stars Dakota Johnson, Chris Evans, and Pedro Pascal.
Explores a love triangle between a matchmaker, her ex-boyfriend who dreams of being an actor,
and a wealthy playboy surrounded by New York City's money-obsessed dating scene.
Song's second directorial effort after Past Lives (2023), Materialists continues many of her previous
film's themes regarding intimacy, identity and relationships with people in the modern world.
Produced by Killer Films and 2AM, Materialists was distributed by A24 in the
United States and received a limited release on June 13, 2025.
Distributed internationally by Sony Pictures Releasing International, the film received positive reviews from critics and grossed $108 million worldwide,
making it A24's third highest-grossing film of all time, the highest-grossing independent film of 2025 and Song's highest-grossing film to date.
The film explores themes of new york city, love triangle, wedding, class
differences, ex-boyfriend ex-girlfriend relationship.
The tone is emotional and thought_provoking.